spicytricks.com 2014-05-27

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy for www.SpicyTricks.com

The privacy of our visitors to www.SpicyTricks.com is important to us.  
This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.spicytricks.com and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, www.spicytricks.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track userâ??s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

#### DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.spicytricks.com.Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.spicytricks.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site

#### Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.spicytricks.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.  
www.spicytricks.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.  
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.spicytricks.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.  
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs.  However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.  This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.  
**Comments Policy**  
The author does not assume responsibility over comments he did not make on this blog. While comments are welcome from anybody, we reserve the right to remove any comment that is not deemed suitable for publication. This could include but is not limited to objectional and abusive comments. Hate, racist comments, or any other form of prejudice will be removed and the poster will be banned!  
Comments made for sole purpose of getting backlinks or advertizing your/any product will not be accepted. Link to third party website will require moderation and we reserve the rights to edit/delete such links.  
Spam in any form will not be accepted and will be deleted immediately. We may take action against such spammers.  
**Copyrights**  
Supreme caution has been taken to make sure that there are no copyright infringements in terms of the multimedia content and the subject matter that is posted in this blog. If you find anything that could be considered a violation of the copyright norms, please contact me immediately.
